

AlHanouf AlGhanim

Business Administration and Management

A Highly Professional Business administration and management, Studying Master's degree in General Business from American International Theism University with accredited certificates in several fields and distinctive experience in the top levels of management, especially in the fields of Business Administration, Logistics Management, Procurement, Relations, and others. Expert in improving operations, supervising all administrative aspects, and applying the foundations for the development of individuals and companies, including developing administrative and operational strategies, monitoring employees' performance, and achieving sustainable profits, and increasing revenue. Proven records of success in advising senior management in important and critical matters, recommending change, solving problems in the simplest way, and developing growth plans. I utilize wise judgment with exceptional abilities to solve complex issues. Furthermore, I contribute to enhance and identify exceptional growth within organizations; I always exceeded all expectations in extraordinary ways.

\times

AlHanoufAlGhanim7@gmail.com



0562233259



Saudi Arabia, Riyadh

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Great Communication

Contract Negotiation

Projects Management

Team work

Logistic & inventory

Strong Interpersonal

Materials Management

Relationship Management

Presentation Skills

Problems Solving

Technical & analytical

Time Management

EPIC system

SAP System

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Power Point

Microsoft Excel

CORE STRENGTH

Adept at measuring the effectiveness of the outputs, evaluating the performance of employees, and following up on work progress on a daily basis

Exceptional practical experience in overseeing key performance indicators, setting goals and making professional plans by identifying and setting achievable goals, and outlining the tasks and schedules on how to achieve the set goals

 $Aptitude\ and\ judgment\ in\ decision-making\ and\ strategic\ planning\ and\ accomplishing\ growth\ ,\ goals\ and\ objectives$

Skilled in building positive relationships with government and private agencies, stakeholders, and senior management to achieve common benefits and growth

Handling administrative procedures, financial procedures, and operational business

Skilled at developing financial aspects, strategic planning and preparing periodic reports

Depth experience in tracking and applying business and management principles involved in strategic planning, resource allocation, and contract negotiation, team supervision and coordination of resources

EDUCATION

Master of General Business American International Theism University

American International Theism University

05/2022 - 12/2022

Bachelor General Business Major

American International Theism University

01/2022 - 05/2022

United States of America

.United States of America

High Diploma Medical Secretary & Transcription

King Faisal university

12/2005 - 10/2008

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business administration and management

Johns Hopkins Aramco Healthcare

07/2017 - Present

Saudi Arabia , Dhahran

Achievements/Tasks

- Establish and carry out departmental or organizational goals, policies, and procedures
- Oversee employees and give them constructive feedback and suggestions for improvement
- Developing goals for the development team and business growth and ensuring they are met.

COURSES

- Certified International
 Procurement Professional
 CIPP
- The 7 habits of highly effective people (signature)
- Warehouse operations & management
- Success completion if
 Material Requisition Project
 (MRP)
- lst Annual King Fahad Teaching Hospital in Neurosurgical Symposium
- Personal Centered care Training
- Leaders skills- Accelerate your Success
- Presentation skills
- Fire safety
- Infection control Hygiene

WORK EXPERIENCE

Supply chain Materials buyer & expeditor

Johns Hopkins Aramco Healthcare

12/2015 - 07/2017

Achievements/Tasks
■ Raise and issue purchase orders to suppliers

- Expedite late delivery dates, or on occasions cancel/delay
- Update purchase orders in the company ERP/MRP system.

Contract management Advisor

Johns Hopkins Aramco Healthcare

01/2015 - 12/2015

Achievements/Tasks

Develop/ review different types of contracts/agreements for the projects

- Administer the contracts and ensure all terms and conditions are implemented by all projects
- Develop review contracting strategy & plan for different types of projects

Procurement strategic sourcing,

Johns Hopkins Aramco Healthcare

08/2014 - 01/2015

Saudi Arabia, Dhahran

Saudi Arabia Dhahran

Saudi Arabia, Dhahran

Achievements/Tasks

- Manage supplier and material master data information in ERP/MRP system
- Create, maintain, and monitor an identified category which includes a sourcing strategy (performance of targeted suppliers, high-level assemblies, and service part
- Lead the strategic sourcing process of team formation, research, evaluation, and structure

Logistic planner

Johns Hopkins Aramco Healthcare

04/2014 - 08/2014

Saudi Arabia, Dhahran

Achievements/Tasks

- Conduct comparison analysis and present monthly reports to management on data performance to plan.
- General administration filing, queries, claims, checking costs in accordance with departmental requirements
- Monitor order fulfillment

Supplier Relations & Customer Support

Johns Hopkins Aramco Healthcare

11/2013 - 04/2014

Saudi Arabia, Dhahran

Achievements/Tasks

- Enhances supplier relationships by developing and continually improving upon post-award supplier processes
- Provides technical guidance to key stakeholders working within the supply chain
- Promotes and monitors the implementation of an integrated supply chain involving key supply chain stakeholders at all levels of the system

Operational Specialist,

Johns Hopkins Aramco Healthcare

06/2013 - 11/2013

Saudi Arabia ,Dhahran

Achievements/Tasks

- Assisting with the implementation of new processes and procedures
- Overseeing the operations team and assigning tasks.
- Training new employees and ensuring that health and safety regulations are foll

Health Information Management & Medical coding

Johns Hopkins Aramco Healthcare

12/2012 - 06/2013

Saudi Arabia, Dhahran

Achievements/Tasks

- Making sure that codes are assigned correctly
- Complying with medical coding guidelines and policies
- Analyze medical records and identify documentation deficiencies

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Analyst

Johns Hopkins Aramco Healthcare

08/2012 - 12/2012

Saudi Arabia, Dhahran

- Achievements/Tasks
- Evaluating business processes, predicting requirements, identifying opportunities for improvement, and designing and implementing solutions
- Communicating your ideas and goals to cross-functional team members and management in an effective manner
- Analysis of stakeholders

Sr. Executive Assistant

Al Falak Electronic Equipment & Supplies (Aramco contractor)

02/2011 - 08/2012

Saudi Arabia, Dhahran

- Achievements/Tasks
- Coordinating daily calendars of senior managers
- Planning appointments and events
- Acting as the point of contact between executives and employees/clients

Vice President Medical Advisor

King Fahad Teaching Hospital (Internship)

05/2008 - 01/2009

Saudi Arabia, Khobar

- Achievements/Tasks
- Assisting the president and the board of directors to design the Hospital overall mission, values, and strategic goals
- Performs a variety of administrative duties of a complex and confidential nature, Schedules and arranges the Vice President's calendar
- Handles confidential information regarding management, faculty, staff, and/or students and controversial matters including legal subpoenas for information.

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

Native

Professional Working Proficiency

REFERENCES

Available upon request